{
    "title": "Necrosis",
    "author": "ayobami",
    "type": "dcq",
    "course": "chem-path",
    "date": "2024-07-24 20:30",
    "description": "Reviewing your knowledge about one of the ways a cell goes to die; necrosis",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Necrosis is an active process of cell destruction",
            "answer": "false"
        },
        {
            "question": "The affected cell swells in necrosis due to influx of solute and water",
            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "question": "In liquefactive necrosis, the organ maintains its integrity / architecture",
            "answer": "false"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the brain, necrosis usually takes the form of Liquefactive Necrosis due to high levels of microglia",
            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "question": "In the limbs, tissue death is usually termed Gangrenous Necrosis",
            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "question": "When a dry gangrene becomes infected, it becomes a type of liquefactive necrosis",
            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "question": "Caseous Necrosis is a specialized type of necrosis that happens in the legs during a Tuberculosis infection, with a 'cheese-like consistency'",
            "answer": "false"
        },
        {
            "question": "Enzymatic Digestion is the dominant force in coagulative necrosis",
            "answer": "false"
        },
        {
            "question": "Protein Denaturation is the dominant force in coagulative necrosis",
            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "question": "When severe ischemia occurs to most organs, liquefactive necrosis occurs",
            "answer": "false"
        }
    ]
}
